{
    "id": "616cc46431ea45f2ae3a9276732e38a7",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Shakespeare is greater than ………………… playwright.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "any other"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ..................... than I.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. than I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more older",
                "older",
                "elder"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the ..................... . of the two routes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shorter",
                "shortest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the ...................... decision.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wisest",
                "most wisest",
                "most wise"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Hercules was stronger than .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any man",
                "any other man",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two evils choose the ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His clothes are superior …………………. mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Health is ...................... wealth",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preferable to",
                "more preferable to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer walking ………………… riding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}